Hello,
I am back in front of you again today with my
next video, as
I shared with you in the last video that I will
make a video on health insurance in a more informative and better way, so today
I am trying to do it for you,
subscribe to this channel, channel Ghrit
because it is very important for us to subscribe,
Meghnad subscribe, if there is any problem, then
definitely subscribe, so you should
know that there will be a war, nothing will happen, you might have liked it a lot,
but before that, still I would
like you to watch my videos,
nothing can happen, so you subscribe,
so I will start
with those who are not because now
you have to understand that
some things are not covered in health insurance,
you are seeing the list,
these are five such things that are usually not subscribed, the
first point is a
mental illness, a
mental illness in English does not mean a proper
mental illness, the accused in mental
subscribe, this is not subscribed, the
second point is this half inch subscribe button does
not subscribe, but subscribe, those who
subscribe to their subscribe,
subscribe, good things,
golden of your thinking because hepatitis is
such  Things which must be subscribed first,
where to subscribe,
I have a viral fever, I am unwell,
I am going to the doctor, the doctor should subscribe for me, then
subscribe again, my medical expenses,
such expenses require
more patience, if we are going to talk about it, that is
why I have made specific and
that the expenses are not covered normally, but hence, the
products of some companies are such
that you subscribe and
subscribe, hence they are not covered, the
next important thing which is
not covered in health insurance, I
call it cosmetic treatment like getting the eye
line removed, skin treatment,
any grafting, is there any dental
treatment, in this also
some products are subscribed in the industry
that we have to pay that much money for entry subscription,
if you do
not subscribe, then subscribe, if
someone dies due to an accident,
during subscription, if I am subscribing
and do not get relief, this is called
channel TV, then these are
congenital diseases, you must
know about them, till a little bit simple,
that diabetes will stop you in the event of an accident
Type-1 diabetes, what does it mean by type-2 diabetes,
type-2 is that
someone got it cleared at an age, my age is, so
today on Thursday, subscribe to some other
subscribe button and
subscribe, it does not subscribe,
it is very important
that there are some companies which say that if you
also take your policy, you do not know
after that there will be many dishes and you will not forget
the mission, it is okay, another congenital digit
example of India also works that there is
no problem in the placement of the kidney,
here the right kidney of some people is so
small that we can do that with normal follow-up, this is the
kidney of Doctor Mukesh Maurya, this is also an
unknown Italian store, so some company Ramesh
Yadav may not have Friday, but there were some companies,
they did not subscribe from this point
and subscribe